In this video, I'm going to be talking about what I call over under.
Now this is a pretty difficult crystal stick trick--crystal stick trick.
It will take some practice, and it will take some thinking just to figure out what exactly you're trying to do.
First off, I'll just show you what it looks like.
This is over under.
You're going to start from horizontal circles, and go over, under, just like that.
Now, it might be hard to figure out what I'm doing from how it looks.
What I'm actually doing is I'm in a horizontal circle, I catch the crystal stick in the center of it, with my control stick.
Now I'm going to follow the crystal stick as it spins.
I'm going to keep my control stick ninety degrees to the crystal stick, follow it as it spins.
Now, I'm not sure if I can actually break this down into parts, and execute it, but what happens I'll spin like this, spin it under, and then because of the way my wrists and arm work together, I'll be over for one rotation, and back down to under.
Again, this is something you just need to try and see if you can work out for yourself.
To switch into it, you're doing horizontal circles, catch in the center, follow the crystal stick out, over, under, over, under.
If you see, I'm always keeping my control stick ninety degrees perpendicular to the crystal stick, just following the stick around with my wrist like that.